Guide to the Cornell University International Agriculture records, 1952-1980.
Cornell University International Agriculture records
- Series XIII. University of the Philippines - Cornell University Graduate Education Program(UP-Cornell) - Chronological File
  - Ford Foundation Appraisal of Program to Date, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Viabliity Factor for the College of Agriculture - University of Philippines, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Reynaldo Resurreccion, 1969-1973 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Chancellor Samonte and Dean Bernardo Visit to Cornell Campus, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Annual Report - Ford Foundation in the Philippines, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Proposal for Research on Agricultural Diversification and Trade, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Philippines Publication - Sweet Potato Marketing in the Philippines, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Philippines Publication - Summary of 19 Economic Surveys on Food Consumption, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Philippines Publication - Coconut Socio-Economic and Marketing Study, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Philippines Publication - Feasibility of a Feed Mill in Zamboanga City, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Philippines Publication - Feasibility of a Feed Mill in Cagayan de Oro, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Philippines Publication - Production and Marketing of Palay Seed, 1977 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - ASUDIAP, 1978-1979 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Dean Call, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - CALS Associate Dean, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Operations, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Public Policy Coordinator, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - C.U.Administration, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Development Fund, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Agricultural Economics, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Agricultural Engineering, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Agronomy, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Animal Science, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Communication Arts, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Ecology, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Education, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Environmental Studies, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Extension, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Finance and Business Office, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Food Science, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Geneva, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Instruction, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Mann Library, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Media Services, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Microbiology, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Minority Affairs, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Natural Resources, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Plant Breeding, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Biometrics, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Plant Pathology, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Pomology, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Poultry, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Research, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Rural Sociology, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - Vegetable Crops, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 33)
  - Vegetable Crops Research Proposal to Rockefeller Foundation on Dry Beans, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 34)
  - Deans and Directors Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 35)
  - Department Chairmen, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 36)
  - CALS Faculty, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence - A, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 38)
  - CALS Advisory Council, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 39)
  - Affirmative Action, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 40)
  - AID (Agency for International Development), 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 41)
  - AID - Biological Nitrogen Fixation, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 42)
  - AID - Basic Assistance Activities for Agricultural and Rural Planning and Policy Analysis, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 43)
  - AID - Cornell Workshop, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 44)
  - ADC (Agricultural Development Council), 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 45)
  - Alabama A and M University, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 46)
  - American Farm School, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 47)
  - Aquaculture at Cornell, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 48)
  - CALS 75th Anniversary, 1979-1980 (Box 46, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence - B, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - BIFAD (Board of International Food and Agricultural Development), 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Biological Sciences, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - BTI (Boyce Thompson Institute), 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - C, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - CIS (Center for International Studies), 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - CIS Executive Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - CIS Decision Making Project, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - CIS Rural Development Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - CIS Rural Development Participation Project, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Computer Activities, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - D, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - DIAL (Departmental International Agricultural Leaders, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Dominica Government, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - E, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - East-West Center, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Ecuador, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence - F, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - FAO (Food and Agriculture Organization), 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Food and Life Science Quarterly, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Ford Foundation, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - G, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Gennadiev, Alexander (Soviet Scholar), 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Graduate School, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence - H, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Hebrew University, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence - I, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - IADS, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - IARD, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - India, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - International Science and Education Council, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - International Professorship, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - International Student Office, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - International Rice Research Institute, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - Italy-Bellagio Workshop, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence - J, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 37)
  - Japan, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence - K, 1979-1980 (Box 47, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence - L, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Lomba, Pedro Paulo (Brazil), 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - M, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence - N, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - NASULGC, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Nigeria, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Northeast Directors International Agriculture, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - O, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - P, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Peace Corps, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - PEPSICO, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Philippines, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Philippines University, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Poona University, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Professors at Large, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Puerto Rico University, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - Q, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Queretaro University - Mexico, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - R, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Ranmuthugala, Janaki (Sri Lanka), 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - S, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - SEARCA, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Soil Restraints Conference and Correspondence, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Southeast Asia Program, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Soviet Union, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Science, Technology and Society, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - SUNY, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - SUNY Campuses, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence - T, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Thailand, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence - U, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - USDA, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Veterinary College, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Villareal, Ruben L., 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence - W, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Women in Development, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - World Food Issues Workshop, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Chronological - January to June, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Chronological - July to December, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - University of the Philippines College of Ag. Annual Report, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - University of the Philippines College of Ag. Annual Report, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - University of the Philippines College of Ag. 50 Years of Scientific Agriculture, 1909-1959 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - University of the Philippines College of Ag. Annual Report, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Livestock and Poultry in the Philippines Terminal Report, 1952-1957 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Abstract Bibliography of Corn - Laguna, Philippines, 1946-1955 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - CSA - Colloque sur le Riz Symposium on Rice, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Agronomy Terminal Report of H. A.MacDonald, 1959-1960 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Horticulture in the Philippines Terminal Report of L. H. MacDaniels, 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Third Annual Report Cornell-Los Banos Contract, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Fourth Annual Report Cornell-Los Banos Contract, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Fifth Annual Report Cornell-Los Banos Contract, 1952-1960 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Sixth Annual Report Cornell-Los Banos Contract, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Final Report Cornell-Los Banos Contract, 1952-1960 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - First Annual Report Contract Phillipines College of Forestry and C.U., 1958 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Terminal Annual Report Contract Phillipines College of Forestry and C.U., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Rice Production in the Philippines - Student Manual, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Tomato Production in the Philippines - Student Manual, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - General Botany Lecture Syllabus Part I, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Terminal Report of the Visiting Professor of Agricultural Education, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Brochure on Schistosomiasis (Snail Fever), 1958 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Report on Agricultural Extension Education of the Philippines, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Report on Agricultural Economics of the Philippines, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Report on Local Government of the Philippines, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Agricultural Educaton at the Philippines College of Agriculture, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Report on Horticultural Crops - W.C.Kelly, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Entomology Terminal Report - B.V. Travis, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Marketing - Terminal Report L.B. Darrah, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Report on Advancement of Engineering Science in Philippine Agriculture, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Annual Report - Research and Teaching in Local Government, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Vegetable Crops - T.L. York, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Bean and Pea Production in the Philippines - Student Manual, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Management of Resources for Research Report by G. Fred Somers, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Annual Report Vegetable Crops by H. MacDonald, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Report on Animal Products for Human Food and Improved Philippine Agriculture, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Swine Production in the Philippines - Student Manual, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Household Insects - Entomology Syllabus, U P College, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Guide Materials for Homemaking Courses in High School, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Monthly Bulletins U.P. College of Agriculture - Los Banos, 1957-1960 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Proceedings of the Symposium in Search of Breakthroughs in Agricultural Development, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Proceedings of the Symposium Toward More Progressive Barrios, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Philippine Agricultural Research System, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Philippines-U.S. Workshop on Scientific and Technological Cooperation, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Second Philippines-U.S. Workshop on Scientific and Technological Cooperation, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - NFAC (National Food and Agriculture Council) Bulletins, 1974-1978 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Peace Corp Program, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Education for Development, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Joint Workshop on Technology for Rural Development, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - National Agribusiness Development Project, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Masagana 99 - Management Information, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Philippines Nutrition Survey of the Armed Forces, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 60th Diamond Loyalty Day and Alumni Homecoming, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Philippine Agrarian Reform Program, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Interview with Halsey Knapp, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Interview with W. Myers, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Integrated Rural Development Prospectives, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Research in Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries in the Philippines, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Philippines Recommends for Rice, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Series XIV. University of the Philippines - Departmental Files
  - Agricultural Botany (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Agricultural Chemistry (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural Economics, ca.1964-1970 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Agricultural Education, ca.1960-1970 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Agricultural Engineering, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Agricultural Information and Communication (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Agronomy, 1964-1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Animal Husbandry, 1967-1972 (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
  - Applied Math (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Entomology (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Farm Operations, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Food Science and Technology, 1964-1971 (Box 16, Folder 13-14)
  - Home Technology, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Horticulture, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Humanities (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Plant Pathology (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Rural Development Project (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Soils (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Professors and Instructors at the College of Agriculture University of the Philippines, 1963-1965 (Box 16, Volume 1)
    Alphabetical by Department
  - Household Furniture - Staff Houses UP-Cornell Project (Box 16, Volume 2)
    Inventory of furniture by location and room
  - Plaque given to the New York College of Agriculture, Cornell University from the College of Forestry, University of the Philippines, June 20,1960 (Box 16, Frame 1)
- Series XV. Alphabetical File Files
  - A, 1966-1976 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Agricultural Development Council(ADC), 1968-1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - ADC - Continued, 1970-1977 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Afghanistan and Kabul University, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
  - AG International, 1974-1976 (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
  - Alumni Office, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - American Council on Education, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - American Friends Service Committee, 1966-1976 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Asian Association of Agricultural Colleges and Universities, 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Asian Development Bank, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Asian Foundation, 1966-1967 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - B, 1968-1976 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Bahia, University of, 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 14-15)
  - Biological Science, 1971-1975 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Brazil, 1965-1977 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - C, 1971-1976 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - California - International Agriculture Program, 1963-1973 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Center for International Studies(CIS), 1974-1976 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - CIS Ad Hoc Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - CIS - Esmann, 1969-1976 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - CIS Executive Committee, 1966-1976 (Box 19, Folder 23-24)
  - China, 1973-1976 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Columbia, 1969-1973 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Constraints on Increasing Agricultural Production in the Tropics: Research and Implementation Needs, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Course Offerings in International Agriculture - Brochure, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 2A)
  - D, 1972-1976 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - E, 1972-1975 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - East West Center(Hawaii), 1965-1976 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - East West Center - Food Institute, 1970-1976 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Educational Projects, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Education and Cultural Affairs, Burea of, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Education and World Affairs, 1966-1970 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Empresa Brasileira de Pesquisa Agropecuaria (EMBRAPA) Brazil, 1976-1978 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Energy, Food, Man and Environment, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Environmental Studies Program, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Exchange Programs, 1974-1976 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - F, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Forms, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations(FAO), 1961-1976 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - FAO - Cornell, Animal Science, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - FAO - Thailand, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Fellowships, 1966-1974 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Fulbright - Hays, 1974-1976 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Film Committee, 1965-1975 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Florida, University of, 1972-1975 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Ford Foundation, 1960-1975 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    Pamphlets and Newsletters
  - Ford Foundation - Problems in International Economic Order, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Ford Foundation - General Correspondence, 1963-1976 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Ford Foundation - Overseas and Travel Policies, 1963-1974 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Ford Foundation - Brazil, Indonesia, Lebanon, Pakistan, Columbia - Venezuela, Thailand and Tunisia, 1963-1973 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Ford Foundation - India, 1967-1974 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Ford Foundation - Indian Agriculture, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Ford Foundation - Mexico, 1964-1971 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Ford Foundation - Lagos, Nigeria Gamble, Rep., 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Ford Grant Final Summary - Cornell - University of the Philippines College of Agriculture Program, 1963-1973 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Foreign Area Fellowship Program, 1968-1972 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - G, 1968-1976 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - German Marshall Fund of the United States, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Ghana, University of, 1966-1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    Includes Report of the Special Committee on Extension Ghana, January, 1971 by D.W. Barton
  - Graduate School Announcement, 1965-1975 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School Field Representatives, 1969-1976 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Guam, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - H, 1974-1976 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Hawaii, University of, 1972-1975 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Hawaii, University of - Consultant's Seminar, May 11-15, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Houston, University of, 1965-1970 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Home Economics, College of, 1966-1974 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - I, 1970-1976 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Ibadan, University of, 1969-1974 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Ibadan, University of - Memo of Understanding, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Illinois, University of, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Indian Council of Agricultural Research Possible Collaboration in Soils and Water Project, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Industrial Labor Relations(ILR), 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Institute of International Education, 1967-1975 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Inter-American Foundation, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - International Agriculture - Association of U.S. University Directors of International Agriculture Programs(AUSUDIAP) - General Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - International Agriculture - AUSUDIAP Annual Meeting, Michigan, June 9-11, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - International Agriculture - Departmental Leader, 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - International Agriculture Development(IAD) - Assistant Director Search, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - International Agriculture Development(and Rural Development), Field of, 1963-1976 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - International Agriculture Development(IAD) Publications, Policies on, 1694-1975 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - International Agriculture Development(IAD)- Seminar Committee, 1964-1976 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - International Agriculture Development(IAD) - Seminar Speakers, 1964-1976 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - International Agriculture Development Service - Proposal to Rockefeller Foundation, 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - International Development Assistance and International Education, 1968-1969 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges/Agency for International Development(NASULGC/AID)
  - International Development Research Center, 1973-1976 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - International Development, Society of and Development of, 1965-1974 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - International Development Studies, Committee on State University of New York(SUNY), 1970-1974 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - International Food Education, League for, 1969-1974 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - International Institute for Rural Reconstruction, 1965-1975 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - International Living, The Experiment of, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - International Population Program, Cornell University, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - International Programs at Cornell University by Irwin Sanders, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - International Programs, Report of Committee on (CALS), May, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - University International Science and Education Council, United States Department of Agriculture(USDA), 1972-1976 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - International Students, Office of, 1964-1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - International Studies Information Service, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - International Visitors, 1963-1976 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - International Visitors, Office of College of Agriculture and Life Science(CALS), 1961-1972 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - International Visitors, Monthly Report, 1963-1974 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - International Voluntary Services, 1963-1972 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Iowa State University, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Iran, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Irrigation Research Proposal, 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    G. Levine, M.L. Barnett et al
  - J, 1970-1976 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Johnson Foundation, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Joint Commission on Rural Reconstruction(JCRR), 1972-1976 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Jurzykowski, Alfred Foundation, Inc., 1972-1976 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - K, 1968-1976 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Kellogg, W.K. Foundation, 1969-1970 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Keys Seminars, 1975-1976 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - L, 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Ladd, Robert, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - M, 1972-1976 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Malaysia, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Massachusetts, University of, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Master Plan, 1973-1975 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Michigan, University of, 1968-1974 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Midwest Universities Consortium for International Activities, Inc., 1971-1976 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Minnesota, University of, 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Missouri, University of, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Murty, V.V.S., 1968-1970 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - N, 1969-1976 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - National Academy of Sciences, Ghana, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges(NASULGC), 1962-1974 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - NASULGC - International Affairs Committee, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - NASULGC - Land-Grant College Meetings, Washington D.C., November 13-14, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - NASULGC - Land-Grant College Meetings, Houston, TX, November 9-12, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 39)